Richard Montoya Londoño

Address: Cra 47C # 76B sur 09 - Phone: 311 706 7977 - E-mail: richard.a.montoya.l@gmail.com

Software Developer

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

20/11/2020 -15/02/2021

Cilab Digital

(Medellin- Developer

Colombia) Functions: Elicitation of requirements, development of websites using different technologies, server

configuration and management, relational database

management.

Savant BPO.

05/02/2018 -20/11/2020

Developer

(Medellín-Colombia) Functions: Linux server management, development of new internal solutions, network management and deployment to production, database management,

and process automation.

13/03/2016 -28/07/2016 (Medellín-

INSITE S.A.S,

Developer

Colombia)

Functions: Javascript development, AngularJS and creation of unit test, test integration, bug fixing and deployment automation. Development of Node.js and

deployment automation. Development of Node.js and Python bindings. Management of NoSQL databases.

EDUCATION

2012-2018 Software Engineering (8 semesters)

Medellín-Colombia Universidad de Antioquia

2019-Ongoing Software Engineering (Ongoing)
Medellín-Colombia Universidad Nacional de Colombia

2014 Professional Backend Course

Colombia Mejorando.la (Platzi)

PROFILE

Passionate for Software development and the Infrastructure surrounding it. Bilingual and learning my third language, with experience of taking software from requirements to production.

Interested in Agile methodologies, with good teamwork skills, and a constant desire of keep learning and improving.

TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript, Angular JS, React, Material design, Typescript, Redux, CSS, Stylus, HTML5, Pug, Jinja, Python, Django, Flask, PHP,

Codelgniter, Laravel, Node.js, Express, AWS, Linux, MongoDB, MariaDB, MySQL, Oracle DB,Curl, BASH, Selenium.

LANGUAGES

English: High Spanish: High German: Low

INTEREST

Software Architecture Data Science Business Intelligence Embedded Systems Languages History

SKILLS

Problem Solving Teamwork Logical Thinking Dedicated Responsible Proactive Fast Learner